quintup.com 2017-09-19

# Privacy Policy

It is our policy as a company to protect and respect your privacy. This privacy policy together with the documents that are referred herein aim to set out the general basis on which the personal data that we collect from you will be processed and made use of. Please go through the entire page very carefully so that you can understand our practices and views with regards to your personal data and how as a company we aim to treat it. We try to keep certain basic details when you make a visit to our website and as such recognize and respect the importance of keeping such details secure and letting you know whenever we are accessing your personal data.

You need to appreciate that this privacy policy only applies to this website. If you get to another site through a link, you will be subject to the policies of that particular provider. So, it is important to go through page so that you can get the most out of the use of our site and the services and products we offer.

### **What Information Do We Collect From You?**

We normally collect details from you when you fill out a form or register on our website. When you are ordering or registering on this website, you will be asked to enter your names or email addresses for authorization purposes. You can still make use of our website unanimously though.

### **How Do We Make Use Of The Information You Give Us?**

Any of the information that you offer us might be used in any of the following ways;

  * To personalize your experience – This information allows us to effectively respond to your needs.

  * To improve our website – This information gives us feedback on what you perceive of our website. Therefore, we strive to develop our website based on what you feed us with.

  * To improve customer experience – This information allows us to effectively respond to customer requests and better support our clientele

  * To process transactions – The information that you leave on this website will not be sold, transferred or exchanged to any other company or third party for whichever reason.

  * To send periodic emails – The email address you provide will be used to process your order requests and send you periodic mails about your performance or status on our website. However, this only happens with your consent at hand.

### **How Do We Protect That Information?**

We have implanted a myriad of security measures aimed at maintaining the safety and security of your personal information.

### **Do We Discuss Your Information With Third Parties?**

We do not trade, sell or even transfer your data to outside parties at any one time. So, when you post any information on our website, it will be treated with a lot of respect and privacy. We comply with the law and respect your confidentiality in all our business dealings.

### **Privacy Policy Online**

The privacy policy in this case only applies to the information that has been collected through our website when you are online. It does not cover for information collected offline.

### **Your Consent**

By making use of our website, you consent to all the details herein. To learn more you can contact us by email: jasminestevexx@gmail.com

Privacy Policy

Rate this post
